Isn't this too far?
It will increase the travel time.
Your house is good enough.
We'll be tying the knot
and starting a family.
The kids will need
their own rooms, won't they?
You persuaded him, didn't you?
Smart move. You've mapped out
your life meticulously.
Just put up with him for a few years,
then claim half his fortune.
Your life will be set as you approach 40.
Wrong. I'll claim everything.
I won't leave a dime
for Manju and the kids.
Manju isn't likely
to be around in 15 years either.
Once the wedding happens,
I won't wait that long.
There are many drugs
that are undetectable in biopsy tests.
- Will he really marry you?
- Does he have a choice?
I'm waiting to introduce him
to the family.
Once Kittu delivers the baby,
everyone will be cheerful.
Laughter will fill the house.
Dad will be thrilled!
The timing will be perfect!
To stab their happiness-filled hearts?
Correct!
Ladies and gentlemen,
you just witnessed
how this woman bewitched
this middle-aged man
with her enticing youth.
She fell for the wealth,
and he for the youth.
So, they fell in love chasing
what was missing in their lives.
Tell me. Can you fall in love
after just one night together?
Maybe not from the act of sleeping,
but often, due to the lack of it.
They fell in love, and also
fulfilled their romantic desires.
But when their future was in question,
they realised the truth.
Ayesha wanted to get married
and have kids.
But Ashish didn't want
to do these things all over again.
This led to a sad scene
so they broke up and sang a sad song.
Come along…
By the time the sad song ended,
they realised that their love was true.
So they patched up again.
After the patch up,
Ashish had a brilliant idea
that Ayesha should meet his family
so he took her to meet them.
- Manju.
- Ayesha.
My wife.
My secretary.
That lie led to a whole lot of chaos.
He dislikes lentils.
He likes mine.
When the truth was finally exposed,
his daughter's wedding
was almost called off.
While trying to comfort Manju
in her grief,
Ashish got a little too comfortable.
And the fool revealed this to Ayesha.
The fight led to the discovery
that Ashish and Manju never got divorced.
Ayesha left in a fit of rage,
and Ashish stayed back
for his daughter's sake.
Later, Ashish sorted out
his daughter's marriage.
Seeing that sacrifice,
Manju got emotional.
She went to convince Ayesha.
It's hard to accept, but…
If love can't blossom
from one night together,
then how can it fade away in one night?
Ashish got emotional and made a promise
to go through the entire ordeal again.
Everyone thought
this was the end of story.
Everything's sorted now.
So, ready to get married?
What do you mean?
I'm not an orphan, you know!
I've got a family too.
- What are you saying?
- You have to meet them.
Now, watch the story unfold.
Yeah, Mom. I'm heading out today.
No need to send anyone.
I'll manage.
Okay, I'm hanging up now.
I need to finish packing.
Okay, bye.
Nervous?
A little.
But don't worry,
my family isn't too dramatic.
Will you tell everyone at once?
Or one by one?
One by one.
Will your mom be first?
So she can manage the others?
My mom's not like most moms.
She won't handle anything.
She's loyal to just one person.
Her husband.
Once I tell her,
she'll immediately tell dad.
Then dad will pretend
like he doesn't have a clue
and will try to get the details from me.
He will drop hints,
so that I tell him myself.
Then break the news to everyone at once.
It's like an official application
that has to pass through multiple hands.
Everyone knows who it is for
and who gives the final approval.
But following the process is critical.
If I tell dad with the others,
he will feel that he isn't being valued.
And what if his real reaction comes out?
Trust me, it's best kept hidden.
So, mom gets the first reaction
and we get a progressive,
empathetic, understanding
father's rehearsed speech.
I thought your family
was supposed to be chill.
I never said they're dramatic.
It's all about the process.
Following the process is important.
I'll manage.
I'm not a coward like you.
Don't worry.
Who's your daddy? Your daddy?
I said, "Who's your daddy? Your daddy?"
- You're here.
- What does it look like?
I'll give you a smack!
Don't act all smart.
Is he training for some competition?
Fitness. For me.
Mom, please! I don't want to hear it.
That over-the-top energy might backfire.
You'll face competition
if his focus ever drifts.
Immature guys get distracted.
Experienced men are fixed on one goal
throughout their lives.
Ayeshu!
No, Dad! You're soaked in sweat.
Training for the Olympics?
Ever since he found out
he's going to be a grandpa,
fitness has become an obsession.
He's excited but somewhat shaken.
He's still in denial
that he's going to be a grandpa.
Stop it, Rajji.
I do all this for you.
What?
We're educated, progressive people.
We're modern.
She's my college sweetheart.
And this is how she became your mother.
Give me that.
Listen…
- Where's Kittu?
- In her room.
What did my brother do to you?
How could you let him?
I liked what he did,
but what I'm going through now is torture.
No one's listening to me!
Everyone's doing their own thing.
Listen, I didn't want to deliver
at our home in Gurgaon
so I wanted to go to my parents'
place instead of coming here.
That's where I'm heading
after the sixth-day rituals.
I feel like a ping pong ball!
Your brother is always quiet!
He just works from home
with those headphones on. I hate it!
Vent it out.
You can vent your frustration on me.
I'm here to help you relax.
I've asked the doctor to be on standby.
It can be any moment.
Hey! Take it easy, dear.
Don't exert yourself.
Why are you just standing there?
Can't you help her?
What would you like for breakfast?
Won't someone ask me as well?
I flew nine hours to get here.
Don't they serve food on the flight?
Father-in-law, your daughter is visiting.
Give her some attention.
She's getting jealous.
What do you mean?
Rajji, isn't she like my daughter too?
How could she say that?
Mother-in-law, please take him away.
I'm the one who's pregnant,
but he's the one acting hormonal.
You know how it is, dear.
He is feeling vulnerable right now.
Make your special omelet.
Coming right up.
Make one for her too.
Done.
Mom, ask dad to add extra cheese.
If you want to talk privately,
just say so.
Do I look stupid?
Brother, should I say it again?
So, any news on the due date?
What did the doctor say?
Is it happening today or not?
You don't get real time updates
for these things.
He said it'll happen today,
but it depends on the baby's mood.
What happened?
Planning to return?
I want to call the baby's uncle.
Nice, taking advantage of the situation.
What's wrong? Call him.
I'm here. I'll handle everything.
You just saw how important I am.
They listen to everything I say.
- Where is he from? India or London?
- London.
- How long have you been together?
- Six months. We live together.
Six months?
You're living together…
You're living together and didn't tell me?
Fine, I'm the sister-in-law after all.
I'll probably tell your brother.
I can't be trusted.
Why are you hesitant to introduce him?
He is a bit older.
How old?
Old enough that I won't get approval
without family drama.
So, I'll sandwich this bad news
between a slew of good news.
It won't seem so bad.
What if they don't like the good news?
They'll fling the sandwich in your face.
Not when they are holding the baby.
You want to use
my unborn child as leverage?
Shameless!
You said you came here
to reduce my stress.
- Is my baby your shield?
- I'm the aunt, I have the right.
- Shouldn't the baby get to meet the uncle?
- Future-uncle.
Actually, maybe-future-uncle.
I can't do it.
No one will accept this.
It will be a big scene!
- I can't handle this.
- You can. I trust you.
Just keep quiet till your delivery.
- I--
- Lips sealed.
Any chance it'll be today?
It's the baby's delivery date,
not the bank's EMI
where the date of deduction is scheduled.
I know, Ayesha.
I also have two. Remember?
I just want to know
if I should reschedule,
or cancel my ticket.
Cancel it for now.
You can't come before the baby's delivery.
- Visit later.
- Okay.
Okay, bye.
Father-in-law!
Sprouts are light.
This won't cause indigestion.
Try it. It's good.
I want Dal Makhani.
Such a glutton!
You just ate.
Is it my fault?
I'm eating for two now.
Don't pay attention to her.
I'll order it.
I want to eat at a diner.
Which diner opens at ten in the morning?
Don't worry, dear.
They'll open.
I'll make sure of it.
How is it, sir?
Good.
Thank you, sir.
Would you have chilly curry?
- I'll get it right away.
- Thank you.
Spicy food helps speed up delivery.
- Yeah.
- You arrived so late,
and now you're in a hurry to be an aunt!
Yeah!
She's not in a rush to be an aunt.
Once the baby's here,
she'll announce she wants to get married.
She's living with a man older than her.
How long have you been living together?
Six months.
What does the boy do?
He's in finance
and owns an investment firm.
What happened?
I think it's time.
- Get the car!
- Let's go. Confirm with the hospital.
Careful.
One, two…
- Come on.
- You'll be fine. Easy.
We'll get there. Come…
What happened?
Nothing, Father-in-law.
I think it was gas.
It's gone now.
I am okay now.
- Let's go home.
- Yes, of course.
Careful. Easy.
Ayeshu, I have a question.
What did we do that you felt
you couldn't tell us?
It's us.
You know you can talk to us
about anything and everything.
It's been six months,
and you didn't tell me.
You told Kittu but not me.
I mean, when did this distance
grow between us?
We've been friends
rather than father-daughter.
Right?
We're friends.
Don't take it personally, Rajji.
I'm sure she had her reasons.
It was complicated.
I thought it would be tough
to explain on the phone.
You two might not understand.
He's older and divorced, so…
Ayeshu, divorce is no longer a stigma.
Sometimes marriages don't work out,
and it's better to move on.
We're educated, progressive people.
We are modern. We understand.
And I've always maintained
this atmosphere in the house
where we can all chat like friends.
- Isn't it, Rajji?
- Of course.
Remember how supportive I was
when you told me
about your first boyfriend?
Unlike other fathers
who transform into tyrants.
I am hurt, Ayeshu.
I am hurt.
Rajji, we must've done something wrong
because our daughter
doesn't have the confidence
to confide in us.
You know, I've always
encouraged and respected
open, honest conversations.
He has two kids.
A girl and a boy.
They live with his ex-wife, Manju.
See? How simple it is.
Honesty and truth.
That's all that matters to us.
Isn't it, Rajji?
How old is he?
It doesn't matter, Rajji.
Age is just a number.
I am sure if Ayeshu has chosen him,
she has good reasons.
Ashish is a great guy.
You'll really like him, Dad.
I am sure I will.
I'm your friend.
Always remember.
Not just your dad.
Friend.
I want to meet him.
Call him.
All good at home?
Chandigarh has changed drastically.
- Did you tell your family everything?
- Of course.
I'm not a coward like you.
In fact, they are really looking
forward to meeting you.
Mom, Dad.
Ashish.
Hello.
- Did you have a good trip?
- He didn't travel by train, Rajji.
Congratulations on soon
becoming grandparents.
- Thank you.
Ayeshu, show him his room.
Let him freshen up.
Rajji, please arrange breakfast.
I hope you all are okay
with me staying here.
I mean, there's a baby's coming
and you don't know me well.
I don't want to make
anybody uncomfortable.
- I mean, I can stay in a hotel.
- What are you saying, dear?
We're not that orthodox.
Feel at home, please.
We're educated, progressive people.
We are modern.
Come.
'Dear'?
Why do I feel
like you've lied to your family?
I didn't lie.
I told them
a selective version of the truth.
What did you say my age was?
I said you're older,
but not your exact age.
I won't tell them that
until after the delivery.
Are you crazy?
The delivery date is uncertain.
Should we keep lying till then?
We won't lie.
Let's just not tell the whole truth.
Half-truth is still a lie.
No.
It was you who lied
when you called me your secretary.
I told them you're my boyfriend.
That you're older,
divorced, with two kids.
I just didn't mention your exact age
or how old your kids are.
I'll tell them those things,
but after the delivery.
What if it takes longer?
- Are you going to keep lying?
- What do you mean?
I won't lie. I'm warning you.
- I'll tell the truth if anyone asks me.
- Brilliant!
So, you're trying to be honest here?
Why didn't you try it with your family?
Did I not cooperate?
Did I not?
I endured silently.
Everything!
I watched you eat those lentils.
The same lentils you refused
to eat when I made them.
I spoke up so confidently
that you don't like lentils.
I was heartbroken
when Manju said you liked hers.
And you
ate her lentils right in front of me!
Did you not?
Shall I list all the things
I quietly endured?
So, keep your honesty to yourself.
I won't reveal your age
before the baby's delivery!
Ayesha,
lying to my family was my mistake.
Nobody blamed you for it.
You are younger, I am older.
If you lie, they'll think I pushed you.
Our relationship will start
with doubt and a lack of trust.
Very mature.
Again, let me repeat.
- Keep this maturity--
- Ayesha,
I won't lie.
I won't candidly reveal my age.
But I won't lie if someone asks.
Look. I love you, but I won't lie.
Don't tell anyone
unless asked outright. Promise me.
I won't tell anyone unless
they ask my age outright.
Not even a hint.
You'll try your best to keep it a secret.
How old did Ayesha say he was?
Age…
What age did Ayeshu say?
Everyone in this house is deaf!
When your little sister confessed
that she likes someone,
you should've listened carefully!
She's coming.
Ask her.
It sounds rude to ask her directly.
Ashish. My brother.
- Hi.
Please, call me Rohan.
Yeah. Calling you 'brother'
would sound weird.
I'm sure you're younger than me.
- Come.
- Yeah.
Thank you.
He's so sweet.
How can anyone divorce such a sweet man?
- Right?
- I'm sure they had reasons.
Right?
It was a mutual decision
between Manju and Ashish.
They were together since college.
At first, they wanted the same life
but eventually,
they wanted different things.
Do the kids live with their mom?
- Yes.
- A boy and a girl.
His only regret
is that he had to leave them behind.
But he's a great dad.
The kids are very close to him.
Like friends.
Like you and I.
Friends!
Your kids must be adults now.
No matter how old they get,
they'll always be children
to their parents.
That's what you keep telling us.
- How long have you been divorced?
- It's been three months.
The divorce was recent,
but they were separated since a long time.
They just never signed the papers.
Only when we decided to marry
did it hit us that he needed
to be legally divorced.
So he did it right away.
How long have you two been separated?
- What happened?
- I think it's time!
Get the car! Call the hospital!
- I'll get the hospital bag!
- Let's go!
Careful.
Naina, get the hospital bag quickly.
Come on.
What happened?
- It was just gas.
- Oh!
Relieved?
Did you notice, Rajji?
- We were questioning the boy--
- Man!
Right.
We were questioning the man
and she was answering for him.
If we're being polite
and not asking directly,
is she going to take advantage of it?
Isn't that wrong?
Fine. Let's be direct.
Rajji, no more politeness.
We'll ask him directly.
Relax, Rajji.
Didn't you hear?
They've decided to get married.
We'll have to handle this tactfully.
Rohan, I was thinking we should start
investing for the child's
education right away.
Makes things easier.
You're right, Rajji.
It's a good idea.
When Ayeshu went abroad,
I remember one pound was almost Rs. 100.
I remember it was 101.48 rupees exactly.
What about when you went abroad, dear?
It wasn't always so high, was it?
I don't remember--
What do you mean?
It was exactly Rs. 101.48
when Ayeshu went abroad for her studies.
It was Rs. 101.48.
- I think--
- He didn't go there to study, Dad.
He went to work.
He earned in pounds and spent in pounds.
And since he was well-off,
he didn't worry about conversions.
Ashish, try the lentils. They're superb!
He doesn't like lentils.
Tell them.
I don't like lentils.
Who on earth doesn't like lentils?
How can you trust a man
who dislikes lentils?
Wasn't he sending his earnings
to his children in India?
Didn't he check the value of pound then?
And what was that about being rich?
Are we poor because we
remember the exchange rate?
Take a hint.
If we aren't asking you directly,
it doesn't mean you should
keep changing the subject!
Do you know anyone
who doesn't eat lentils?
This is ridiculous.
Everyone eats lentils.
I'm telling you, Rajji.
I'm going to ask him directly now.
Ayesha told me you like single malts.
Let's have this tonight.
Twenty-five years.
The older the liquor, the better.
I wish that also applied to people.
Rajji? Ayeshu?
Come on.
It's a big day today.
Ashish is visiting for the first time.
It's our first drink together.
Rajji, I think you should have one.
Ice? Water?
Nothing.
You know how to respect liquor.
Okay, I'll also have it neat then.
I'll have to respect the age
of the liquor.
Ayeshu?
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
Yes.
Sir, like you asked,
we have retrieved Ashish Chawla's details.
I told you to tell the concerned officer.
The matter needs more consideration.
Born 2nd May, 1974.
Fifty-one years and 5 months old.
Wife Manju Chawla lives in Kullu,
runs a resort.
Two kids. Ishika, 25 years old,
and Ishaan, 22 years old.
Hold on.
That's okay.
But we have to do due diligence.
They married in 1999,
and in 2005, 20 years ago,
Ashish shifted to the UK.
He became a citizen in 2011.
Okay.
You're spying on him?
Really?
- Ayeshu--
- No, seriously!
Ask whatever you want.
Ask him directly.
What do you want to know? Interrogate him.
- Ayesha--
- You stay out of it!
How dare he do this?
I think it's…
It's not.
Where are you going?
Ask away.
I'm sitting right here.
What happened?
Don't want to talk?
The girl's lost her mind!
He's just 1.5 years younger than me.
And she has become so manipulative!
Who taught her this?
It wasn't us for sure!
We never played
the good-cop bad-cop routine.
We've always been good cops.
Lying isn't in our DNA!
Who lies in this family? Not you, not me.
I'm telling you, Rajji.
He has bewitched her!
He gives me devilish vibes.
Not at all, Rajji.
She's taking advantage
of our progressiveness.
We never imposed restrictions or hit her.
Let me teach her a lesson right now
and she'll snap out of it!
She has no shame!
The man is just a year younger than me.
And she's blaming us!
She started this drama
and we are the villains!
All tactics, Rajji.
She wants to make it a fight.
She wants war.
Otherwise, she'll have to sit
and talk and be cornered.
I'm sorry for my language,
but there is no logical explanation
for this stupidity.
It is stupidity!
What 'sorry', Rajji?
This is stupidity!
Let me…
I'm going to shoot him.
- I will shoot this rascal!
- No.
No. I'll kill him!
- I am telling you, I will kill--
- Rajji!
They've been living together
for six months
and have decided to marry.
This is not the 90s.
You're not Amrish Puri from the 90s,
nor is our daughter Simran,
who wouldn't marry
without her father's permission.
If I threaten her
that I'll swallow poison,
she'll tell me to slit my wrist
and lie in the tub
saying it would be easier.
You know her.
No one can force her to do anything.
We'll have to handle this calmly
and strategically.
Look at this.
If they come to talk,
the power balance will shift.
You have no idea
what you're dealing with.
Yes?
We need to talk.
Come inside.
Coming.
Alone.
Yes.
Come in.
Why did you lie to us?
Why did you lie?
I didn't lie.
Not revealing the truth is also a lie.
I told you the truth.
And if you wanted more details,
you could've asked directly.
It's called respect.
You wouldn't know its meaning.
But it's important for people
who are respected and mature.
Didn't you feel bad
exploiting this moment?
Didn't it occur to you
that it's a huge moment for your dad?
You shouldn't treat him
this way right now, but--
Ayeshu,
I don't want to get into
why you hid the truth or lied to us
or picked this particular moment.
I just want to say,
I've waited 27 years for the moment
when you'd tell us
you've chosen your life partner.
That I'd meet him.
That I'd intimidate and threaten him.
That I'd tell him
I'll shoot him if he doesn't
take care of you for life.
I've always imagined
that the guy you bring over
would be a great man,
the right man, very loving.
He'd make you happy every day,
every moment.
You know, that he'd be
a great man like me.
And then I'll accept him like…
I've dreamt of this all my life.
He is a great guy, Dad.
He's right for me.
He loves me a lot.
Always. Every day.
He makes me happy every moment.
He is a great man like you.
I didn't want him to be so similar
that you'd end up
with someone my age, Ayeshu.
Ayeshu, I've always
respected your decisions.
And you know
I'm not some old orthodox guy.
But I cannot come to terms with this.
I won't be able to convince myself.
This is wrong.
I can't let you make this mistake.
I can't be a part of this mistake.
Just because he's older than me,
and the same age as you
you changed your views
on education and progressiveness.
You're modern, aren't you?
Ayeshu, it's not just
about the age or the divorce.
He left his wife and two little kids
and moved to another country.
What's the most he's done
besides sending money?
Didn't he have a love marriage
with his ex-wife?
He must've promised
to take care of her too.
But he abandoned his wife
and their children.
Abandonment is in his nature.
A man can change his intentions
but not his nature.
He's a deserter!
And you're comparing him with me?
If you've already decided
who he is and what he is like…
I won't waste my time or yours
trying to explain that you're wrong.
Because there's nobody
more intelligent than you, right?
And I'm sorry I compared him to you.
Because you're a great guy.
And we're sewer insects
who lack the sense
to decide what is right and wrong.
Ayesha, if I'm speaking to you patiently
it doesn't mean
you can speak to me this way.
Mind your tone.
Nice.
We're analyzing tones now.
Let it go.
I didn't come here seeking permission,
nor do I need it.
Thank you for your time.
How can she talk to me like this?
Do not test me!
And your idea
about not needing permission…
If I wish that he never sees you again,
he never will.
He'll disappear from your life
in the next ten minutes.
Great!
So we've resorted to threats of power now.
Do it.
- Ayesha, you have no--
- Father-in-law!
Believe me. It's time.
For real.
I can't believe
I'm going to become an aunt.
My baby feels intimidated.
Didn't you come here to reduce my stress?
You're a witch!
Don't touch me.
Breathe, dear. Take deep breaths.
Where is Ashish?
Should I get out? I'll get out.
I am not important.
I can come back later. Let him sit.
I'm sorry.
Let me deliver this child.
I'm going to beat
the daylights out of you!
You came to reduce my stress.
If anything happens to me,
get her married.
Don't say such crazy things.
- Nothing will happen to you.
- What if something does?
Raise the baby yourself,
and not at my parents' place.
- Nothing will happen.
- What if something does?
- Promise me.
- We promise.
It's a girl!
Congratulations!
- You've become grandparents.
- It's a girl.
Congratulations.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you. You are?
He is Ashish. My college friend.
He lives in London.
He's staying with us.
The timing is just a coincidence.
That's a good thing.
It's a rare opportunity
to see a friend become a grandpa.
- Come on, let's go.
- Yes, please come.
- Do you want to hold her?
- Yes.
Dear God!
She's so cute.
I am your grandpa.
Give her to me.
She's so sweet.
My turn now.
Hi!
Oh, my God.
Careful.
- Hold the neck.
- You're such a cutie.
Thank God you look like your mom.
Let the grandparents hold her.
Look at her.
- Mini Kittu is here.
- Careful…
What do they want to imply
by using the baby?
Do they think
she's the only baby in the world?
Come on. Let's make our own baby.
Right now, right here.
Are you crazy?
Go inside, stay with Kittu and the baby.
This is not the time for a fight.
What is this behavior?
What are you doing?
I don't want to argue with you.
If you can't understand what a huge
moment this is for the family,
then I won't waste my time
trying to explain that.
I won't waste my time on you either.
I'll seriously smack all of you!
I won't care whether
it's my daughter or my husband.
Is this the time to fight?
Kittu's parents are here.
Don't you two have any sense?
She's right.
- You stay out of it!
- Quiet!
Kittu will stay with her parents
after the sixth-day rituals.
We'll talk about this then.
Come on, say 'bye' now.
Kittu needs to rest.
Ayeshu, stay here with Rohan.
Come on.
Listen, I'll go back.
I don't want to spoil
this occasion for your family.
Very nice. Very mature.
That's the problem with you.
You are too mature.
You are not going anywhere.
You won't find a better opportunity.
Just them and you.
Show some of that young spirit.
Woo them the way you wooed me.
Bye, dear.
They flung the sandwich
in your face, didn't they?
Pretty hard.
Plan failed.
I am screwed.
Aunt caused a rift.
Even the uncle got rejected.
Turn on the radio.
Enjoy the next song…
What to do?
I've ended up with an old man
I've ended up with an old man…
What to do?
Ayesha wants me to impress
her parents like a 25 year old.
Am I young enough to do that?
As per the Gita,
only the body ages, not the soul.
Your body may have aged,
but your soul is still young.
You can do it.
I have full faith in you.
What do you think I should do?
What do you think you should do?
This isn't a therapy session.
I'm asking because I'm confused.
You know my mind doesn't work
unless I charge hourly.
Help me help you.
I'll send you the money.
Now give me an idea.
First, stop blaming your age.
You're smitten by a younger girl,
so you can't be afraid
of impressing her parents.
You are the intense type.
Romance is not your forte.
Learn from Shah Rukh.
Remember DDLJ.
Shah Rukh flew from London to Punjab
to convince the father in his style.
Her marriage was fixed
and the father was a scary type.
The girl was scared of him.
But in your case, the daughter is fiery.
Use the same confidence
you used to win her
to win her parents now.
Trust me. Trust yourself.
Transfer the money, things will be fine.
If you want to discuss
anything else, just call.
Remember, this is your safe space.
Bloody loser!
Let's get ready quickly
and bring her home.
Yeah.
Good morning.
I made breakfast.
Potato curry, chickpeas,
sweetmeats, and fried bread.
Ayesha said you love to eat.
Coincidentally, I love to cook.
I mean, I love cooking.
- His cholesterol level is high.
- Mine too.
What medications are you on?
Ecosprin.
Same.
We've got cooks, you know.
I know.
But my mom always said
the real flavor comes from love,
not the spices we add.
Sir, they say you've ordered this.
Just keep it coming. Keep it there.
I ordered it.
Actually, that's not it.
Something weird happened today.
I went for a morning walk,
and bumped into a minister
who turned out to be my dad's old friend.
He gave me all this stuff.
What was I going to do with sacks
of wheat, rice, and sugar?
So I brought it here.
There's a newborn in the house.
Many guests will be visiting,
so it will be useful.
Your dad's childhood friend?
Yes.
So, let me get this straight.
An 80 year old man
was lugging around sacks of grain
in the morning, just like that
and ran into you.
Then he thought,
he should gift the items
to his childhood friend's son?
Is that what happened?
And you thought,
you shouldn't refuse an elderly man
who is also your dad's friend
so you brought it all here?
Yes.
Rajji and I watched it together
back in 1995,
right after our wedding.
Three times. In Delhi.
You must've watched it
with your ex-wife too.
Ayeshu wasn't even born back then.
What did you get me into, Shah Rukh?
Rajji, did he hear us talking
about Simran and her dad yesterday?
Simran must have told him.
Does he know Kajol?
How would he know Kajol?
Our daughter must have told him.
Have some, Sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law…
Sister-in-law?
Mom.
Mom…
Mom?
Sister?
Sister!
Rajji, is he Ayeshu's uncle?
No…
Age-wise, I should call her Anju.
But since she's Ayesha's mom,
I don't know how to address her.
You should've thought about that earlier.
Who's your daddy? Your daddy?
I said, "Who's your daddy? Your daddy?"
Did you do all this?
So sweet, thank you.
Here's a reminder,
when Kittu comes home after six days,
we're throwing a party.
You must attend. No excuses.
- I…
- Rakesh, you tell him.
He has to come.
He will listen to you.
I'll tell him.
Tell him now.
You're coming with us. That's final.
You're coming with us and that's final.
Bored?
Don't worry about me.
Just keep your distance.
Or your dad will get mad.
He'll get mad anyway.
The truce we called for Kittu
and the baby's sake ends today.
Let's see what tomorrow brings.
You're such a coward.
The weather is nice today.
Yeah.
She's my daughter!
Sir, you're mistaken…
I am sorry.
I didn't know.
Look, I'm really very sorry.
Sir!
I'm sorry, sir.
I said I'm sorry.
- I told you she's my daughter.
- Sir, I apologized.
She's my daughter. I told you!
- Sir, I'm sorry--
- He was staring at my daughter.
My daughter…
I'm sorry, sir!
Go on, hit him.
Hit who you really want to.
Let it out!
Hit him!
Hit me!
It's my fault.
You've got such a huge problem! Really?
Have you ever thought
how people judge this relationship?
What names would his friends
call you behind your back?
I'm not able to deal
with how cheap it makes you look.
The first time we met,
I was drunk out of my wits.
He found me passed out in his bathtub.
He respectfully moved me
to the guest room.
He didn't make a wrong move.
I don't care what people think
because I trust him.
Don't you care
about the respect I've earned--
How is it your respect
if my choices can affect it?
Why is it bothering you
so much how others see us?
You're just hiding behind them.
You aren't able to watch this.
If you truly believed this was right,
I'm sure you wouldn't care
about what anyone thought!
You believe that I'm wrong.
That we're wrong!
In your view,
this whole relationship is cheap.
Cheap young girl…
Rich, perverted old man…
Cheap love.
Right?
This is how you look at us.
Say it.
Say it out loud.
Cheap young girl!
Rich, perverted old man!
Cheap love!
You…
Ayesha, if I may.
You shouldn't have said what you said.
Are you done giving him
a word-for-word update?
You two gossip like old women.
He asked me what happened, so I told him.
Of course you would.
And I'm sure you made it
sound like it was all my fault
because I am immature.
Not all of it.
Considering how he explained it,
anyone would think most of it was on you.
I totally understand.
He does that with me too.
Because he wants to show how mature he is.
Why are you two picking on me?
I'm just saying he's a father.
Any father would have a problem with this.
We knew this would happen.
Your actions haven't solved anything.
They've only made things worse.
How did it make anything worse for you?
Are you interested
in the wife or the in-laws?
I've always been here. I still am.
We're together.
So how did it affect you?
They weren't your in-laws.
That hasn't changed.
I suffered the most.
My parents--
They will always be your parents.
Ayesha, you're angry right now.
And I know they aren't understanding.
Right now, you may think
you can live apart from them.
But tell me this.
Can we live like this?
When we get married,
won't you miss them?
When we have kids,
won't you want them to hold them?
To bless them?
Life is long, Ayesha.
If staying together
means breaking up with them
then what kind of relationship
would that be?
The heroes of our generation
don't run off with the heroine.
The father grants his permission.
Very nice.
Very mature.
Explain that to him, not me.
Heroines from my generation
don't waste their lives
over their fathers' egos!
It's not his ego.
It's just a little hard to understand.
He must be equally worried.
You think he's enjoying any of this?
None of it matters to him.
He's just waiting for me to crawl back
and beg for forgiveness.
Sorry.
I'm sorry, Dad.
I'm really sorry.
I'm really sorry, Dad.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
Enough.
I didn't come here to make you emotional.
Come home. Both of you.
There's an event.
We'll get to spend some time together.
Dad, this is Raunak. Ashish's best friend.
- Hi.
- Hello. Hi.
I wish I could go with you
but I'm busy with work.
Enough with the drama.
I'm inviting you.
So am I. Please.
Well, since you both insist, of course.
Rajji, am I a good father?
What do you think?
Why do you ask?
Did I do right by you and the kids?
Always!
Except for one mistake, Rajji.
This is what he wanted.
To take my daughter away from me,
so I can't protect her.
And I let him.
He wanted me to leave Ayeshu alone,
so I wouldn't stand by her.
And I did.
What Ayeshu said
weren't even her words.
That was him.
Could my daughter
ever say such things to me?
Never.
When I held her for the first time,
I made her a promise.
That I'd always protect her.
At any cost.
Even if I had to burn
the whole world down.
But because of my anger,
I broke the first vow
I made to my daughter.
But it's okay.
My ego isn't bigger than my daughter.
I won't let that man win.
I will protect her.
Who's your daddy? Your daddy?
Who's your daddy? Your daddy…
I'll keep my promise, Rajji.
I'll keep my promise.
Who's your daddy? Your daddy?
I said, "Who's your daddy? Your daddy?"
I said, "Who…"
Welcome to my humble home, gentleman.
You come from a rich family.
So you really love him.
Just for two days, find a way
to shut your trap and zip it.
Welcome, Raunak. How was your journey?
Fine, thank you.
I wanted to talk to you guys.
Yes.
You know how families are.
If they catch wind of your relationship,
it'll become the focus of everything.
They'll bomb me and Anju with questions.
They'll ignore the function
and indulge in gossiping.
You know, not everyone
is as educated, progressive,
and modern like us.
Don't get me wrong.
But can we pretend that you're
my friend, visiting from London?
I know, we'll have
to tell them eventually.
But if we tell them now…
- Please don't misunderstand me.
- No, you're right.
It's just for a few days.
Let's stick to this story.
It's simpler.
Great, thanks.
Won't they ask why they've never
seen this friend of yours before?
He's my friend, they will ask me.
I'll handle it.
If he's an old friend,
he should've visited you before.
But it's his first time meeting everyone.
You're underestimating
how self-involved people are.
Ayeshu will keep telling him
about everyone.
And before anyone asks anything,
if he calls their names
and asks if they recognise him,
no one will deny it
because it seems rude to do so.
So everyone will pretend like they do.
Any concerns?
Great.
Who's your daddy?
Everything should be in place.
Keep it there.
Put things in order.
Silver-golden, golden-silver.
Set this up.
The table's empty. Bring the vase.
Go…
- Hello.
You are…
Uncle!
Uncle Babbi!
How are you?
How do I look?
The moment I stepped in,
brother put me to work.
He wants me to check on things.
Again, who are you?
Babbi, you've grown so much
that you don't remember me?
Ashish…
Uncle, you're getting old.
What's wrong with your memory?
He is dad's childhood friend.
Ashish.
Right. Mr. Ashish.
You two were in the same class.
I recognise you.
- Babbi, he's…
- Mr. Ashish.
My memory's not so bad
that you need to remind me.
I've known him longer than you have.
Mini, he is Mr. Ashish.
Brother and he were classmates.
Hello.
Hello!
We haven't met before.
Did you attend Rohan's wedding?
Hundreds did.
You wouldn't remember everyone.
Let's continue this later.
There's much to do.
The guests are arriving. Let's go.
Sister!
Grandma, Aunt Anita, Tia and Dia.
Hi.
- We've been looking for you.
- And texting you.
I left my phone in the room.
- Grandma!
- My dear…
Recognise me, Anita?
What about you, ma'am?
No.
Your memory, I tell you…
I am Ashish. Rakesh's childhood friend.
Whoever you are,
this is the first time I'm meeting you.
So, Mr. Ashish,
Rakesh's childhood friend…
Why did you ask if I recognised you
when we've never met before?
Mom, he must've heard a lot about us,
leading him to believe we've met.
Actually, that could be true.
But I've never heard of you.
- Where are you from?
- Around here,
but I've been living
in London for a long time.
You flew all the way from London
for your friend's granddaughter's
naming ceremony.
Why didn't you show up
for your friend's wedding back on…
December 20th, 1992.
Sunday. The temperature was 21 degrees.
The nuptial rounds
were supposed to start at 2:15 p.m.
but began at 3:47 p.m.
Neither did you show up
when his children were born.
Neither Rohan,
born on 20th October, 1993,
Tuesday morning at 2:13.
Nor Ayesha, born 13th March, 1996,
Wednesday at 5:58 pm.
That day, India played
Sri Lanka in the World Cup,
and we watched the match
in the hospital waiting room.
Aravinda de Silva scored 66, Tendulkar 65.
Srinath and Jayasuriya
took three wickets each.
And his kids' naming ceremony--
- What the--
- Grandma!
- Grandma, he--
- Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
I'm asking him, so he will answer.
He just went too far.
He shouldn't have challenged my memory.
So let the man answer,
and he's free to go.
Ma'am, if I may?
Actually, they recently
patched up after college.
This was the first major function
at his friend's house
since they patched up--
- What do you mean by a patch up?
- What?
You said they patched up again.
What's that about?
It's okay.
It's been a long time.
We can tell her. Right?
See, ma'am.
Your daughter Anju was a beautiful girl.
I mean, she still is.
A beautiful lady. Both of them, actually.
They've taken after you.
I heard that your daughter
had many admirers in college.
You know how the world is.
I'm sure you understand.
Two friends, one girl.
Love triangle.
Friends torn apart by a girl.
Broken friendship.
Usual stuff.
But years have passed.
Everyone has grown up.
It's all in the past now,
so they patched up.
Till death do us part, kind of thing.
I'd buy that version.
My sister broke many hearts in college.
Did you get your answer, Grandma?
About who knows whom and for how long?
Why should I care
about who knows whom from when?
And who showed up or didn't?
He challenged my memory.
I was just proving
that my memory can never be wrong.
Sorry, Grandma. It won't happen again.
I'm sorry.
Sorry, ma'am.
Sorry, Anita.
As per the birth chart,
her name should start with 'R'.
Okay.
I have already named her Ira!
It's just a formality, dear.
Her name is Ira.
It's just procedural.
I told you about it.
Okay.
Shall we get up?
Start the party.
There won't be any party.
You're not allowed
and I won't dance alone.
Who wants to see drunken
middle-aged men dance?
The Punjabis are here!
Yo Yo Yo Yo
- Karan Aujla, Avvy…
- Get me that skirt, love
You already know, baby
Get me that skirt, love
I did this 30 years ago.
That's the problem.
She wasn't born 30 years ago.
She didn't see it.
Oh, my love! What do you crave?
You're the drug I crave
Jatt boys rock Versace shoes
And shiny earrings
He's a fierce lion, full of guts
With seven rifles ready
Got three obsessions, you know
Every Jatt lad's got that glow
White horses, brown girls,
Black luxury rides
Jatt boys rock Versace shoes
And shiny earrings
He's a fierce lion, full of guts
With seven rifles ready
White horses, brown girls,
Black luxury rides
Get me that skirt, love
Yeah, get me that skirt
Karan Aujla!
Power in a Jatt's chest
Louis to Dior, all dressed
You talk a lot, babe, stop that ride
You don't get bored of the guys
Never miss a chance,
Come with bullets and a dance
Call me up, girl, if you want to romance
She's shy, but she's teasing
Look into my eyes, I'll get you high
Got a villa for two, shining wide
My boys are real, we don't hide
No spoon-fed lives, no fancy plates
Just white horses, brown girls
Black luxury rides
White horses, brown girls
Get me that skirt, love
Yeah, get me that skirt
Touched you once, now I'm high
You fair one, got mischief in your eye
I've gone mad after you
And you for me
Every day feels like Diwali
Got three obsessions, you know
Every Jatt lad's got that glow
White horses, brown girls
Black luxury rides
Oh, my love! What do you crave?
You're the drug I crave
Adi, I'd like you
to meet my special guest.
- This is Raunak.
- Hi.
- Ayeshu's boss.
- Hello.
This is Ashish, my college friend.
- Hello, Ashish Uncle.
- Hi.
Adi is my oldest and closest friend's son,
also Ayeshu's oldest and closest friend.
Isn't your dad here?
Mom wasn't feeling well.
So dad couldn't come.
He sent me instead.
I am glad you showed up.
Come. Let me show you your room.
- Lovely meeting you, Uncle.
- Same here, dear.
Let's go.
He must be the only father in the world
who's invited a boy
to seduce his daughter.
Don't you sound too negative?
The poor guy came all the way
to London to pacify her.
He's the son of a friend.
You should take people
at face value as well.
You're an idiot
when it comes to face value.
It wasn't an episode of Boogie Woogie
where we'll give him points
for his smooth dance.
All of that was for wooing the girl.
Look, if that's the way you feel,
talk to Ayesha,
and tell her this is wrong.
Don't be crazy.
It will cause friction again
between the father and daughter.
No daughter would like to know
that her father is a liar
and is making a fool out of her.
I can't do that to her.
Let him dance.
She won't be serenaded by his dance.
Are you sure?
According to me,
he should be getting the girl.
The boy's young, handsome, talented,
he's making an effort, flirting with her.
I am actually proud of the boy.
I wish I had a son like him.
Ayeshu.
Give this to Adi.
Get me that skirt, love
Yeah, get me that skirt
Listen. Mom has sent this towel for you.
Are you sure she only sent the towel?
Or was it just an excuse to send you?
She handed me this
as I was heading to my room.
Oh, we're neighbours.
Isn't she afraid now
that something might happen
between us if we stay so close?
When we were younger,
she'd always be scared
that if we played with each other
too much, you might get--
Such rubbish!
- How are you?
- I am great.
- And you?
- Awesome.
Smile.
- Okay?
- Show.
I've got something for you.
What?
Uncle. Who told you?
Instagram.
Can you play the guitar?
Sort of.
See. Talented.
He should be getting her.
Play something.
No, I am not that good.
Just an amateur.
I learned it during COVID
by watching some videos.
I am really not that good.
You put in so much effort to learn,
you should show off a little.
Play something awful
so we can enjoy making fun of you.
I want to pass my time
Chasing sunsets in your eyes
Oh!
And you can have the right
To leave me frozen, hypnotized
Oh!
There's nothing I can think of
That can save me from the brink of
Being incomplete forever
Nobody touches deeper
How do I get to keep her closer?
Through every rise and fall
To her, I give my all
To be with her, always forever
Only you
Only you…
How sweet!
You guys chill.
- I have to finish packing.
- Packing?
You just got here today.
Already?
We hardly got to spend time with you.
Sorry, Uncle. But I have to go.
Dad is all alone.
Mom isn't keeping well either.
How will dad manage work
and take care of mom alone?
The function's over anyway.
I have no reason to stay.
Ayeshu, you tell Adi.
Our requests don't have any value anymore.
He might stay back if you ask him to.
Stay back. Drop the attitude.
Did you get two suitcases
for a single day?
Ask me politely.
Please stay back.
Please.
Not only you
Not only you…
And that imbecile learned it
during COVID on YouTube?
Not possible.
Don't worry.
She won't be wooed by guitar
strumming and singing.
Why would I be worried?
He's not trying to woo my girlfriend.
She's going to be my wife.
Doesn't seem so.
You're so screwed
You're so screwed!
Get ready quickly, guys.
We'll head to the local market
for shopping.
But we're going hiking.
Who's going hiking?
Me, Ayesha, Tia and Dia.
You may go shopping.
Okay.
I'll stay with Kittu.
The four of you can go hiking,
and the rest can go shopping.
Why would I go shopping?
I'll stay here with you.
Please come.
You don't visit India often.
Sister, ask him to come along.
Please come along.
Okay.
The thought of going on a hike
seems like a good idea,
but in the end, it turns out to be bad.
This is just the beginning.
We still have 80 per cent to go.
Are you single?
What?
- Are you single or is there someone?
- There is.
What's the problem?
I never said there's a problem.
If that was true,
he'd be here, meeting everyone.
If he isn't here,
it means there is a problem.
I am single.
Then why did you lie?
I'm afraid that you might
start hitting on me.
It doesn't matter to me.
I'd hit on you if I wanted to, regardless.
I don't care
whether someone's single or committed.
Good. That's the spirit.
Do you want me to hit on you?
Are you going to bore me
like this all day?
We want you to hit on us.
We want to see how you do it.
We want to see your game.
- When did you get so hot?
- I've always been hot.
Not always.
My memory is not that bad.
You were pretty, cute, and fun too.
But never hot.
When did you start becoming hot?
Since the time you set your sights on me.
Try this.
Yes, I'll try this.
The color is lovely…
Shall we move?
Yes. We'll move to the shoe shop next.
Shoe.
What's up with you?
Fogg…
Wow!
- What a great sense of humor!
- Thank you.
Single or committed?
I am not looking for a partner for life.
I need a partner in life.
We have one life.
I want to spend it with a girl
who doesn't think
of marriage as settling down,
but as the beginning to explore life.
I don't want to live like an old couple.
I want someone
who wants to see the world.
Make mistakes, fight
and not make life boring
in the name of maturity.
Basically, she'd want to fly, Ayesha.
Soar…
I haven't found anyone like that.
That's why I'm hitting on you.
You said you would've
hit on me regardless.
That you don't care
if I'm single or committed.
I don't care
if you are single or committed.
But my commitment matters.
I am a decent man. I never cheat.
But if someone else cheats
and falls for me,
then that's not my moral responsibility.
You know, you're a dustbin of wisdom.
I know. I am pretty hot.
Show me that one…
I seriously feel pity for us today.
How sadistic is this?
Sending the girl on a hike
with the boy so he can impress her.
Fine.
But dragging us to shop
for clothes and shoes and torturing us--
If he weren't Ayesha's father,
I would have given him an earful.
I told him we'd stay behind.
I wasn't insisting on going on the hike.
Bloody old man!
Uncle, how come you're up?
Can't sleep?
I'm not sleepy, dear.
How was the shopping? Had fun?
Too much.
Uncle!
Dad has some sleeping pills.
Should I get you some?
No, thank you.
I will sleep eventually.
You should also go and sleep.
You must be tired.
Good night, Uncle.
Good night, dear.
Respectful boy.
Adopt him.
That donkey is riding a horse,
trying to impress Ayesha, and you…
- Show it!
- What are you doing?
I can't endure any more humiliation.
Show them your physique as well.
Why are you feeling humiliated?
Humiliation by association.
Second-hand humiliation.
It's like smoking.
Second-hand humiliation is more
harmful than direct humiliation.
Leave it. Come on.
Aunt, how about going
to the discotheque tonight?
What will I do at the discotheque?
See, I told you.
She trusts you girls
can take care of yourselves.
You said she won't let you go.
I told you that if Ayesha
and I are with you,
she won't stop us or try to tag along.
- They are not going anywhere.
- I'm not going either.
Shut up! We're not talking to you.
Let them go, Aunt.
I promise, no alcohol for them.
Let them go. Ayesha will be with them.
I am sending them because of you.
But no alcohol for these two.
You'll have to tag along for their sake.
I know that you trust Ayesha
and don't want to stir things up
between the father-daughter, but…
What's going on?
Come in.
All okay?
Isn't Ayeshu home yet?
That's the problem with her.
She loses sense of time.
I know what you're trying to do.
Am I wrong?
If you were in my place,
would you have done nothing?
I can't say.
But no matter what the intention is,
a lie is still a lie.
If you don't agree with Ayesha,
just tell her the truth.
What do you think
you'll achieve with all this?
Do you believe true love happens
only once in a lifetime?
When you married your first wife
you must've fallen in love with her.
But it didn't last.
Later, you met Ayeshu
and fell in love again.
I don't believe
that love happens only once.
I also don't believe you truly love Ayeshu
or that she truly loves you.
But if I accept that you do,
even for a moment,
do you really think
that if Ayeshu hadn't met you,
she wouldn't have fallen
in love with someone else?
My truth is,
she lost that chance
when she fell for you.
A chance to fall in love
with someone appropriate,
someone who could stay
by her side for years to come.
And even if I believe
your love for Ayeshu is real,
I'll never believe
you're right for her.
I hold no personal grudge.
All I want is the best life for her.
I'm not doing this
thinking she'll fall for Adi
in a few days.
I'm not crazy.
I'm doing this
so the two of you can see
the life that she could have,
which she is losing because of you.
And if you really are the man
she believes you to be, then…
I love Ayesha.
And trust me,
even I want the best life for her.
But I'm not so selfless
to push her away.
But I promise you this.
If she chooses to leave,
I won't try to stop her.
Thank you.
If you succeed, make sure
she gets the life we both want for her.
The moon must be so jealous tonight.
My girl outshines the moon itself.
Nice, right?
I'm a legend when it comes to corny stuff.
Cringe.
Is there something you want to say?
How do you know?
I know you too well.
Maybe you want to say something
but you're waiting for me to go first.
- Good night.
- Listen.
Jokes aside…
There's a spark between us.
I think you feel it too.
Even if you don't,
you are thinking about the possibilities.
And if you're thinking this hard,
it doesn't seem
like a bad idea to you either.
I know it didn't work out
when we tried it out as kids.
But that was childish.
We had no sense of things.
Now we do.
My heart says we should
give ourselves a chance.
I feel like we're perfect for each other.
If you doubt me, just ask the moon.
I stayed awake all through the night
Awake in your memory
Tell me, love
In thoughts of me
Did you lose your sleep too?
Love found me
When I saw myself within your eyes
You're the one
Who's melted into every dream of mine
Your words have stolen my calm
My peace has been taken away
I stayed awake all through the night
Awake in your memory
Tell me, love
In thoughts of me
Did you lose your sleep too?
I stayed awake all through the night
Awake in your memory
Tell me, love
In thoughts of me
Did you lose your sleep too?
Love found me
Your face, moon-like
My heart longs to gaze at you
You keep me restless, night after night
My power fails, your love prevails
You feel so right, this world feels wrong
No heart should crave this deep
Should I hold it back
Or say it?
These feelings have never
Broken bounds like this
I stayed awake all through the night
Awake in your memory
Tell me, love
In thoughts of me
Did you lose your sleep too?
I stayed awake all through the night
Awake in your memory
Tell me, love
In thoughts of me
Did you lose your sleep too?
Your love feels like an opium haze
My heart runs wild, the night delays
This heart slipped now
Never has it slipped before
These eyes never chased sleep
Like this before
I stayed awake all through the night
Awake in your memory
Tell me, love
In thoughts of me
Did you lose your sleep too?
I stayed awake all through the night
Awake in your memory
Tell me, love
In thoughts of me
Did you lose your sleep too?
Love found me
Your face, moon-like
My heart longs to gaze at you
You keep me restless, night after night
My power fails, your love prevails
Love found me
Ashish.
Ashish, I'm sorry.
Ashish, I'm really sorry.
- I don't know how--
- It's okay, Ayesha.
No. It's not okay.
I know it is not okay.
I don't know how or why,
but I know that I really--
Ayesha.
Don't torture yourself.
I understand.
That's it?
Nothing else?
Say something.
Yell at me.
Scream and curse me!
At least let me apologize.
There's no need to apologize.
Who would know better than me
that feelings change?
But that doesn't erase what we had.
Don't carry the guilt.
What's the point of fighting?
It won't undo anything.
You don't want to fight with me or for me?
I don't have the right
to fight for you anymore.
Somewhere, there must exist a comfort
Where pain cannot reach
And beyond this life
May my eyes forget to weep
Go on!
Running away is the only thing you know!
Somewhere, there must exist a comfort
Where pain cannot reach
And beyond this life
May my eyes forget to weep
Your heart has grown tired of me
My heart knows this
If there's anything left, say it now
Breaking all silences
Saying everything that's in my heart
Yes, I'm saying goodbye
I bid you
A final goodbye
I love you
More than I love myself
My life
I devote to you
I bid you
A final goodbye
I've gathered the courage
To say goodbye
I've built a world for myself
One where your memories no longer exist
Someday
You will think of me
And your eyes will fill with tears
You'll ask God
To bring me back to you
But by then, you won't find me again
I had fought with God
To have you
And then I fought with the same God
To forget you
The one you'll love after me
Don't ever break his heart
I endured the pain
But will he be able to?
Breaking all silences
Saying everything that's in my heart
Yes, I'm saying goodbye
I bid you
A final goodbye
I love you
More than I love myself
My life
I devote to you
I offer you
My final goodbye
Will you marry me?
Tell me. Will you marry me?
Why did I meet you on this journey?
That's the sorrow of my life
If we can't be one again
It's not because we're too broken to be
Maybe she lied to me
But she was never unfaithful
As much as she believed me to be
I was never that fake
I've gathered the courage
Courage to say goodbye
I've built a world for myself
One where your memories no longer exist
I've gathered the courage
To say goodbye
I've built a world for myself
One where your memories no longer exist
I wanted to talk to you.
Go ahead.
I feel like I'm deceiving Ayesha.
What do you mean?
Don't get me wrong.
I love her.
I'm happy that I fell in love with her.
But I can't shake the thought
that I came here because you said
she was stuck with the wrong man.
That's why I tried
to make her fall in love with me.
I pretended to love her.
Though somewhere along the way,
I truly fell in love with her.
I'm happy we're getting married.
But I can't shake the thought
that when she first liked me,
I was deceiving her.
Don't you feel the same?
She told me everything about Ashish.
She didn't want to hide anything from me
before the wedding rituals began.
I think I should tell her everything too.
But then I wonder
if she would understand.
She won't.
Sometimes, for the sake of our loved ones,
we have to hide the truth from them.
We have to lie.
However, a lie like this
is better than a dozen truths
because the intention
behind it is genuine.
Do you love Ayeshu?
Yes.
Then don't tell her anything.
But does she love me?
Sometimes I worry
she's just doing a rebound.
Did you ask her?
You're overthinking.
It doesn't matter how it began.
What matters is that it's right.
I'm sure she loves you.
Thank you.
Good night.
Hi!
Hi.
How are you?
I'm okay.
To what do I owe this call?
I need a favor.
Tell me.
Ayesha called.
What did she say?
She's getting married.
In three days.
She doesn't want to come to London.
So, she wants her stuff sent to the US.
- She tried to call you--
- Ask her the address, I'll send it.
We love the place.
Just give us till the end
of the day to make an offer.
Take your time.
Bye.
Are you sure
you want to sell in this market?
Why sell at a loss?
It's too big for me.
And the reason I bought it for
no longer exists.
Well, as long as you're sure.
I am.
Nothing to say today either?
Raunak told me everything.
Just tell me where to send it.
I'll make sure it's delivered.
Did he just tell you about the stuff?
Have you really thought this through?
You've left me
in no state to think straight.
You broke me completely.
Don't get me wrong.
I'm not saying this for myself.
I wish you were saying it for yourself.
The henna was applied today.
His name is on my palm.
But there's something I need to ask.
I tried not to, but it's suffocating me.
Go ahead.
If love can't blossom
from one night together…
Then how can it fade away in one night?
I guess that's the difference
between your love and mine.
Mine endured and understood…
Yours was swept away by a single mistake.
Still, it was my fault in the end.
I'm sorry.
Take care.
Bye.
I've never seen a bride look so sad.
Congratulations.
You've won.
You've recently become a father.
You'll understand.
I can only hope that someday,
you'll care for her
the way I'm caring for my daughter.
I'll never let that day come
no matter what it takes.
I'll never treat her
the way you are treating Ayeshu.
I'll never cheat her.
Never betray her.
I'll not break my promise.
I'll never deceive her.
Rohan.
And now, the final performance
of the evening…
This is specially for you, Father-in-law.
From your dear Ayeshu.
The darling of this family,
who is going to join
another family tomorrow.
Oh, palanquin bearer
Don't come too soon this way
For a little more time
In my father's arms I wish to stay
Hold back a while, I beg and pray
Hold back a while
Oh, Father
Our bond of love is old
Come, let's dance
For tomorrow I must go
Oh, Father
Our bond of love is old
Come, let's dance
For tomorrow I must go
This is my last night
In your home
Tomorrow
My beloved will take me to our own
I feel the same
As you do today
Hold my hand
Let's twirl and sway
Oh, Father
Our bond of love is old
Come, let's dance
For tomorrow I must go
You are my first love
You know that
And I'm the final love of your life
You taught me to walk
To stand tall
You caught me each time I tripped
No need for blessings
I ask for none
Just hold me close
Your love is the sun
Tomorrow
I'll take care of myself my own way
But hold my hand
And make me twirl today
Oh, Father
Our bond of love is old
Come, let's dance
For tomorrow I must go
Oh, palanquin bearer
Don't come too soon this way
For a little more time
In my father's arms I wish to stay
Hold back a while, I beg and pray
Hold back a while
Oh, palanquin bearer
Don't come too soon this way
For a little more time
In my father's arms I wish to stay
Hold back a while, I beg and pray.
Hold back a while
Oh, palanquin bearer
Don't come too soon this way
Yes, Rajji.
Rajji, where are you…
Wait, Rajji.
What's wrong, Ayeshu?
Why are you crying?
Your dad is fine.
He just got a little emotional.
Mom.
I'm completely lost.
I feel lost.
I'm sorry…
I'm sorry, I didn't want
to trouble you or dad,
but I don't know what I'm doing.
What happened, my child?
What's wrong?
I'm scared.
I feel like I'm being unfair to Adi.
I love Ashish!
And I know…
I proposed marriage
to Adi.
But now, I'm not sure
if I even love him.
I really don't know what I'm doing, Mom.
I don't know what I'm doing.
This happens on the wedding day.
It's normal to get cold feet.
Think about why you asked Adi
to marry you.
There must've been something
you saw in him.
I was frustrated…
With Ashish and with myself.
Then I thought
Adi was the right choice for me.
Don't you think so now?
- I'll talk to your dad.
- No…
Don't tell dad anything.
Please.
He'll be so disappointed in me.
Promise me
that you won't say a word to him.
Promise.
I'll be fine.
I'm fine.
I'm fine!
Are you sure?
No.
But dad is sure.
If he's sure, it must be right for me.
He wouldn't let this happen
if it were wrong for me.
I might not know about anything else,
but I'm sure…
Whether I'm sure about Ashish
or even about Adi,
I'm absolutely sure about dad.
If he thinks it's right,
then it's right for me.
Promise me you won't tell dad.
Promise?
I promise.
What happened, Rajji?
Are you okay?
I made a mistake, Rajji.
A huge mistake.
I broke my vow.
What are you saying?
What happened?
The vow I made to protect Ayeshu.
I couldn't protect her from my own ego.
And while trying to save her,
I couldn't save her from myself.
I became the father
who forgot his vow
to always stand with his children.
To stand by their decisions.
To help them up when they fall.
I got too overprotective.
I took away Ayeshu's right to choose.
You're being emotional, Rajji.
- She was making the wrong decision.
- So what, Rajji?
So what if she was making
a wrong decision?
I'm here if she's wrong.
You're here.
We will handle it.
But this fear of mine
has made me do something absolutely wrong.
What happened, Rajji?
Where are you going?
My daughter trusts me
to do the right thing for her.
I can't break her trust, Rajji.
I will undo the wrongs I've done.
I'll make sure
she marries the man she loves.
I'm going to bring Ashish back.
Handle everything until I return.
Why do you need to go? Call him.
He's not my servant
who'll come and go at my command.
He's going to be our son-in-law, Rajji.
Try to understand.
I have to go there and request him.
I doubt he'll even listen.
Change your clothes.
Are you planning to go like this?
I feel like crying.
I'm 52, trying to convince
myself this is right.
But I can't.
And I feel like slapping you.
It's not enough to just say you will
go through the entire ordeal again.
You have to actually do it all over again.
Logic has to be set aside once again.
History is filled with examples
of madness in love, not sanity in love.
If you love her, then be a real lover…
Don't be a decent lover.
What did you say?
"I lost the right to fight for you."
There's no right to fight.
It's always a fight for your rights!
Till the very end!
If we've grown so old
that we can't even fight for love,
then let's retire.
Retirement's far away.
To hell with decency!
Ayesha is mine.
Are you sure?
You're going there
to stop the wedding, right?
Not to hold her hand
and walk her to the altar?
I'll burn that altar down!
That's my boy.
Let's go.
Lover boy's on the move.
Your father is leaving.
We're in the endgame now.
Do you believe
true love only happens once?
If Ayeshu hadn't met you,
wouldn't she have fallen for someone else?
Someone who'd stay by her side
for years to come?
I love Ayesha.
But I promise I won't try to stop her
if she wants to leave.
If you succeed,
make sure she gets the life
we both want for her.
The moon must be so jealous tonight.
What the…
You wanted a chance. Here you go!
- Have you lost your mind?
- You call yourself a friend?
It's not my fault.
Uncle told me some old guy
has trapped you.
That you needed saving.
So I came to save you!
Did you ask me?
Did you?
Uncle said you've lost
your mind in his love.
That his love has blinded you.
And you turned into some
knight in shining armor!
Did I ever ask you to save me?
You bloody men…
You don't want a way
out of your own stupidity.
Are you going to decide
what's right or wrong for me?
All of you decided on your own
that I needed saving,
and all of you started saving me.
I…
Am I a child?
Don't I have any sense?
And even if I don't, it's still my life!
Who are you?
Are you smarter than me?
I'm sorry.
Honestly…
Uncle persuaded me to do this.
I swear I only think of you as a friend.
- Sure?
- Yes.
I looked up this moonlight stuff online.
Now listen carefully.
You'll do exactly what I tell you.
And if you give anyone a hint
next time I'll use a heel
instead of a slipper.
- Where will that heel be pointing?
- Understood.
So, who else is involved?
As far as I know, your mom and dad.
And now we're going down!
And now we're going down…
Couldn't you catch me properly?
What do you mean? You're so heavy!
- Your jump was all wrong.
- Was my jump wrong?
What's the point of this physique?
I can't. I've got some self-respect.
How can I just lend you my lips?
What if he gets angry?
What if he gets violent?
What if you get excited?
What if the hormones kick in?
What if lust takes over?
Trust me, it won't.
Now shut up.
Timing is very important.
Nothing?
Will you marry me?
Marriage? Are you crazy?
I'm not agreeing to marriage.
You promised to do as I say.
Yes.
You handle my father,
and I'll go, convince Raunak.
Say it…
I had a question.
Am I deceiving Ayesha?
I wanted to talk to you.
I feel I am deceiving Ayesha.
I needed a favor.
Say it.
The henna was applied today.
His name is on my palm.
I clearly told you not to involve me.
Brother, who will help me if you don't?
No!
I don't think
we should have a second child.
What if Ira unfortunately
ends up with a brother?
A brother like him?
It's better that she grows up alone.
At least she won't have
any expectations from him.
What if her brother doesn't support her?
What do I have to do?
I'll never treat her
the way you're treating Ayeshu.
I'll never cheat her. Never betray her.
I'll not break my promise.
What kind of father do you have?
He's got a heart of stone.
It refuses to melt.
My emotional speech
made no difference to him.
What kind of father is our dad?
He is unbelievably tough!
What do we do now? The rituals are done.
We just have one weapon left.
Come on, touch my feet.
Beg me.
I need something in return.
Whatever you ask.
I'll decide the names
of all your children.
- But that's--
- She isn't negotiating.
She's telling you.
I'm sorry, Rajji.
For the first time in 33 years
and hopefully the last,
we are not Rajji.
This one time, you're Rakesh and I'm Anju.
Your Anju is temporarily breaking her vow
of always standing by you.
Because there's another vow
that's more important,
a promise that mothers
make to their daughters.
Mothers never choose anyone
over their daughters.
Make him cry today, sweetheart.
If your dad doesn't melt today,
then I'll lose faith in a father's love.
Don't worry.
He's going to cry a river tonight!
Whether I'm sure about Ashish or not,
or about Adi,
I'm sure about dad.
Hello. Who's this?
Mr. Rakesh, it's Raunak from London.
I don't interfere in others' affairs,
but I'm calling you
because Ayesha is a friend.
Ashish has lost his mind.
He's coming to Chandigarh
to stop the wedding.
- Handle it.
- Hurry up!
Bye.
Rajji, everything's sorted.
Ashish is coming from London
to stop the wedding.
So, I'll wait at the airport
and bring him home.
Listen, don't tell Ayeshu anything.
Let's go to arrivals.
Ashish.
- You can't stop me.
- I didn't come here to stop you.
- I want to take you with me.
- Why?
I'm really sorry.
I misjudged you.
So I've come here to take you home.
- I'm sorry.
- Why are you sorry? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry you came for me,
but I can't go with you.
If I do, Ayesha will think
you brought me here.
She should know I came on my own.
No, it's far more important that
she knows I brought you here.
She needs to know I'm a good father.
I'm sorry, but she needs
to know I'm a good husband.
I'm sorry. You're not her husband yet.
You'll be in the future.
But I'm her father right now,
in the present.
So my priority to win
Ayeshu's respect back is bigger.
Come.
Taxi.
Hold on…
Sir… OTP.
I won't give the OTP.
Do you think I can't make this car move
without the OTP if I want to?
You know that…
I'm really sorry.
You're right.
I'm being selfish.
Go on.
Come on, hurry up!
Step on it.
They must not reach before us
under any circumstances.
Liar.
What's your name?
Sir, it's Milkha.
Step on it, Milkha!
What are you doing?
I thought this is how you get down
on important occasions.
Ayesha!
- Ayesha.
- Ayeshu.
I'm here, Ayesha. I'm here.
I got him, Ayeshu. I got him.
Don't listen to him. I came on my own.
Rajji, tell her that I brought him here.
How does any of that matter?
Why is he even here,
and why did you bring him?
Because I love you, baby.
I can't allow this wedding.
Oh, stop it!
This wedding can't happen
because I won't allow it.
Have you both lost your minds?
The altar's decorated,
the guests are here,
I'm all dressed up.
Why won't the wedding happen?
And how can you listen to him, Dad?
He can't be trusted.
He can abandon me anytime.
He didn't abandon.
I don't think he did.
He probably left because he thought
you were happy with Adi.
He must've left for your happiness.
That's what I think.
- Yes…
- I'm happy with Adi.
He loves me. I love him.
Adi is the right one for me.
What's wrong with you, Dad?
Ayeshu, I know you love Ashish,
- and he's the right one for you.
- Yes.
How much do we really know Adi?
- We don't.
- Yes.
How can anyone fall in love in a month?
- Not possible.
- Baby!
Ready.
You're looking stunning!
He called her baby…
He called your baby his baby.
He's snatching your right.
- My right…
- Give it to me now!
Who are you calling baby?
You're a baby yourself.
- Only I have the right to call her baby.
- Oh, you're here!
Sorry, I didn't notice.
Well, it's quite mature of you
to show up at our wedding to bless us.
I'm not here to bless you,
but to stop this wedding.
Uncle, I know you didn't get closure.
But look at the occasion.
I get it. Closure's necessary.
Once we're married
and done with our honeymoon,
then you can meet Ayesha.
And get your closure.
I won't stop you.
I'm from the young generation.
Open-minded.
Your entire generation is stupid.
My generation is old-fashioned.
I'd never let my wife meet her lover.
What?
In your generation, taking your wife
to her lover was the hit formula.
He's taunting you
about Hum Dil De Chuke Sanam!
Who got her in the end? Answer me!
I'll get the girl today as well!
Look. It's my wedding
and I'm all dressed up.
Violence will ruin my outfit.
I'm staying quiet
because it'll spoil Ayesha's mood.
Otherwise, we'd already
be resorting to bloodshed.
Come on, baby.
- Hey…
- Hey!
Hey, stop!
Father-in-law, you're not ready yet.
The guests have arrived.
Where's your outfit?
Rohan, quickly fetch his outfit.
What's the point
when there'll be no wedding?
What's the point of it
when I won't allow this wedding?
No wedding?
Why isn't the wedding happening?
Whether it's happening or not,
the guests have arrived.
It doesn't look right if the bride's
dad greets them like this.
That's true.
A man's respect is judged by his clothes.
Correct.
Baby, it's getting late.
Dad, think of what people will say.
If the wedding is cancelled
at the last moment,
what will they think of me,
you and all of us?
I don't care, Ayeshu.
To hell with them and their respect!
My respect stays intact
if I'm a good father.
And I'm a good father if you're happy.
I don't care about the rest.
Did you see that?
He just made it seem
like Ayesha's happiness
is his top priority.
Like he does not care about the society.
Ayesha.
For me, your happiness matters the most.
And I don't care about the society.
The only thing that matters to me
is that I love you.
- We are getting late.
- I only care about your feelings, dear.
Dad, feelings can change in an instant.
That's so stupid!
Who said that?
A sensible, mature person.
How could you believe him?
Stay away from such fools!
Ashish said that.
Sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
It's a stupid thing to say.
I take it back.
Dear, he took it back.
Now, you take him back.
No!
I love Adi.
I want to marry Adi.
I love you too, baby.
Ayeshu baby, we're getting late.
It's time to exchange the garlands.
I'll wait for you on stage,
and you quickly walk down
the aisle to a romantic song.
Try to understand, you two.
My feelings have genuinely changed.
I no longer have the same feelings
for Ashish that I have for Adi.
I'll change that.
What if it changes again?
I won't let it.
He won't let it happen, dear.
I know this man.
He's a deserter, Dad.
He'll abandon me.
Ayesha!
I just know that I love you.
And I'll fight for you
against anyone. Everyone.
- I'll even fight with you.
- Listen, Uncle.
Don't call me uncle!
You left! You lost!
It's too late now!
You always complained
that I don't fight for you.
Tell me now. Should I beat him up?
- I'll do it.
- Rajji, stop them.
No. If Ayeshu realizes
how much Ashish loves her
only after seeing Adi get beaten up,
then let him beat Adi.
Yes. Let's decide this once and for all.
Beat me up?
How can you say this, Uncle?
You don't think I can beat him up?
I don't want to ruin my outfit.
Consider his age.
And when did you switch over to his side?
You said he's a pervert, old man--
Show some respect.
He's older than you.
I was about to hit him!
I've had enough.
I'll show him.
They are instigating us.
Don't fall for it.
They want to sabotage our wedding.
Come here, dear.
I'll find you a girl more suitable.
He isn't going anywhere.
Adi, let's exchange the garlands.
Ladies first.
Ayeshu, please listen to me.
Adi doesn't love you.
All this was a petty plan of mine.
It's all my fault.
I'm sorry.
I'm also sorry, Ayesha.
I listened to him
and thought I was making a sacrifice.
You were right.
I should've never left you.
I should've fought for you.
I love you, Ayesha.
And trust me.
I can't live without you.
I don't want to live without you.
Do you believe love happens only once?
If we hadn't met,
wouldn't I have fallen for someone else?
I would have.
And maybe I would've found a man
who'd make me happy
for the next couple of decades.
Now that I've found such a man,
and I am walking towards him,
why are you trying to pull me back to you?
Everyone's in on this plan.
Including me!
You were playing with us.
It was dad and you
who were playing with our lives.
I just made sure we get the life
I want for us.
…probably open a clinic.
I won.
I made sure you did.
Yes, Manju.
Yes, Manju. It's done.
Wedding, what else?
I'll have to marry her
since I got hers cancelled.
Poor baby.
You must be heartbroken.
It's okay. We're there for you.
You girls are getting it wrong.
This was my plan.
They reunited because of me,
since I am a good guy.
Let me talk to her.
Hello, Ms. Manju.
It's Kittu. I've heard a lot about you.
We couldn't have done it now.
Not without you and the kids.
We didn't have the outfit in his size.
And the date was fixed
according to Adi's birth chart.
Yes, please send us
Ashish's birth details.
Did you decide what to call them?
Mom, sister-in-law, sister, apology…
No idea.
How about you call us by our names?
Won't you feel weird?
We're educated, progressive people.
We're modern.
Yeah!
She says
It's an empty bottle,
There's gin in the bottle
And the bottle belongs to a genie
Eyes are red, steps are unsteady
Of whoever's got the bottle
There's redness on the lips,
Abuses on the tongue
Whenever the bottle opens
Open the cap, and a soul escapes
The bottle has a life of its own
Some say it touches the heart
And hides the sorrow
Others say
It calls the beloved
From the depths of the heart
And some say
Once you taste it, you get addicted
But I'm going to drink
Because it fits my budget
Sway on, sway endlessly, oh, drunkard
Sway on, sway endlessly
Dark clouds have gathered
The air is ecstatic
Dark clouds have gathered,
Raise your glass and groove
Sway on, sway endlessly, oh, drunkard
Sway on, sway endlessly
Tonight, fall in love with wine
Rebel against the sermons of the Sheikh
This wine has already
Turned the world upside down
Thankfully,
This wine doesn't have competition
At least, glance kindly
At your companion's face
Come, take refuge
In the tavern to make a life
The moment our eyes meet,
You'll taste the pleasure of youth
You'll know the delight
Of the sweet grape water
Let every gaze turn rosy with desire
Don't stop drinking
Till the world drowns in wine
Don't turn away when the glass is served
When it comes to drinking,
What's there to fear?
There's a storm
In the tavern
There's a storm in the tavern
You should join in the chaos and sway
Sway on, sway endlessly, oh, drunkard
Sway on, sway endlessly
I was sitting in the tavern one night,
My beloved showed up
When complaints and quarrels began,
Damn it, another bottle was opened!
Blood dripped from her eyes,
It shook me to my core
But when I gave her two drinks,
Her spirit bloomed again
She said to me, "You are my lover
Then why do you torment me?
Are you my lover or my killer,
When you strike with a blade?
You used to stay at my home,
Now you wander to the tavern
And when you reach there,
Whose bed do you fall asleep in?"
Sway on, sway endlessly, oh, drunkard
Sway on, sway endlessly
She says
Yo Yo Honey Singh!